<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Ticket System on Jonas Kufner – Power Platform Blog</title><link>https://jonaskufner.com/en/tags/ticket-system/</link><description>Recent content in Ticket System on Jonas Kufner – Power Platform Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.153.1</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jonaskufner.com/en/tags/ticket-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First-Level Support Agent with Microsoft Copilot Studio – AI-powered Ticket Handling in Microsoft 365</title><link>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/first-level-support-agent-microsoft-copilot-studio-ticketsystem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/first-level-support-agent-microsoft-copilot-studio-ticketsystem/</guid><description>Build an autonomous first-level support agent with Microsoft Copilot Studio and integrate it into a ticket system based on SharePoint, Power Apps and Power Automate. The agent answers standard questions, uses a defined knowledge base and reliably hands over complex cases to human colleagues.</description></item><item><title>Ticket System with SharePoint, Power Apps and Power Automate – incl. Automated Status Workflow</title><link>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/ticketsystem-sharepoint-powerapps-powerautomate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/ticketsystem-sharepoint-powerapps-powerautomate/</guid><description>Build a flexible ticket system with SharePoint, Power Apps and Power Automate. Includes status model, module ownership, automated workflow, trigger conditions and form. Ideal for IT teams and internal services.</description></item><item><title>Ticket System with Microsoft 365 – Part 2: SharePoint Reference List &amp; Status Notifications</title><link>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/ticketsystem-microsoft-365-sharepoint-referenzliste-statusbenachrichtigungen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 21:13:42 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/ticketsystem-microsoft-365-sharepoint-referenzliste-statusbenachrichtigungen/</guid><description>Second part of the series on building a ticket system with Microsoft 365 and Power Automate. We add a SharePoint list to store requester email and status references – enabling full checklist usage and automatic status updates.</description></item><item><title>Simple Ticket System with Microsoft Forms, Planner &amp; Power Automate – Step-by-Step to a Quick Ticket Solution in Microsoft 365</title><link>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/ticketsystem-microsoft-forms-planner-power-automate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/ticketsystem-microsoft-forms-planner-power-automate/</guid><description>Build a lean ticket system based on Microsoft 365 in under 60 minutes: form in Forms, tasks in Planner, automation with Power Automate – including Teams notifications and a completion workflow. Tutorial with expressions &amp;amp; best practices.</description></item></channel></rss>