<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>SharePoint on Jonas Kufner – Power Platform Blog</title><link>https://jonaskufner.com/en/tags/sharepoint/</link><description>Recent content in SharePoint on Jonas Kufner – Power Platform Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jonaskufner.com/en/tags/sharepoint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First-Level Support Agent with Microsoft Copilot Studio – AI-powered Ticket Handling in Microsoft 365</title><link>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/first-level-support-agent-microsoft-copilot-studio-ticketsystem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/first-level-support-agent-microsoft-copilot-studio-ticketsystem/</guid><description>Build an autonomous first-level support agent with Microsoft Copilot Studio and integrate it into a ticket system based on SharePoint, Power Apps and Power Automate. The agent answers standard questions, uses a defined knowledge base and reliably hands over complex cases to human colleagues.</description></item><item><title>Ticket System with SharePoint, Power Apps and Power Automate – incl. Automated Status Workflow</title><link>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/ticketsystem-sharepoint-powerapps-powerautomate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/ticketsystem-sharepoint-powerapps-powerautomate/</guid><description>Build a flexible ticket system with SharePoint, Power Apps and Power Automate. Includes status model, module ownership, automated workflow, trigger conditions and form. Ideal for IT teams and internal services.</description></item><item><title>Digital Vacation Planning with SharePoint, Power Apps &amp; Power Automate – Complete Approval Process Step by Step</title><link>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/digital-vacation-planning-sharepoint-powerapps-approval-process/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jonaskufner.com/en/posts/digital-vacation-planning-sharepoint-powerapps-approval-process/</guid><description>Create a complete digital vacation planning solution, including approval workflow, using SharePoint, Power Apps, and Power Automate. Includes vacation overview, day calculation, calendar views, and automated approvals – ideal for IT departments and management.</description></item></channel></rss>